In Britain, it's bottoms up from the week before Christmas till the last firework explodes in the sky announcing the new year.
在英国，从圣诞节前一周到宣告新年到来的最后一朵烟花在天空中爆炸的这段时间里，人们都在举杯畅饮。
The last Friday before Christmas - popularly known as 'Mad Friday' - is one of the busiest periods for the country's pubs and clubs.
圣诞节前的最后一个星期五——俗称“疯狂星期五”——是该国酒吧和俱乐部最繁忙的时期之一。
But it's not just the bars that get busy.
但忙碌的不仅仅是酒吧。
Ambulances and A&E departments around Britain get packed out too.
英国各地的救护车和急诊室也人满为患。
Head injuries, cuts, falls... it's easy to end up hurting yourself or others when inhibitions and composure disappear and your head is spinning due to alcohol.
头部受伤、割伤、摔倒……当自我约束和冷静消失，你的头因为酒精而眩晕时，很容易伤害自己或他人。
Revellers have been warned by the health authorities about the dangers of excessive drinking but indulgence seems to be part of the festivities for some.
卫生部门已经警告狂欢者过度饮酒的危险，但对一些人来说，放纵似乎是节日庆祝的一部分。
The charity Alcohol Concern is running a campaign of abstinence by encouraging people to have a dry January.
慈善机构“酒精忧虑”正在开展一项戒酒运动，鼓励人们在1月戒酒。
Jackie Ballard, the charity's Chief Executive, believes the initiative has been successful in recent years.
该慈善机构的首席执行官杰基·巴拉德认为，这项倡议近年来取得了成功。
She says: "More than two-thirds of people even six months later are drinking at reduced levels having had a month off booze.
她说：“超过三分之二的人在戒酒一个月后，甚至在六个月后，饮酒量都减少了。
But also a study has shown the impact it has on people's health reducing their blood pressure and blood sugar levels."
而且一项研究还表明了戒酒对人们的健康有影响，降低了他们的血压和血糖水平。”
The study by the University of Sussex followed up nearly 900 participants in Alcohol Concern's Dry January campaign and found out that 72% of them had kept harmful drinking sessions down and 4% were still not drinking.
苏塞克斯大学的研究跟踪了“酒精关注”的“1月戒酒”活动中近900名参与者，发现72%的人减少了有害饮酒，4%的人仍然不喝酒。
Fears that a booze-free month would cause people to binge drink the next month didn't materialise.
人们担心戒酒一个月会导致下个月酗酒的情况并未发生。
Moderation seems to be the key to everything.
适度似乎是一切的关键。
The official recommendation for women is not to regularly drink more than 2 to 3 units of alcohol a day.
官方建议女性不要经常饮用每天超过2到3单位的酒精。
That's no more than a 175ml glass of 13% ABV wine.
也就是不超过一杯175毫升、酒精含量为13%的葡萄酒。
The limit for men is 3 to 4 units of alcohol - no more than a pint of 5.2% ABV lager, beer or cider.
男性的限制是3到4单位的酒精——不超过一品脱酒精含量为5.2%的拉格啤酒、啤酒或苹果酒。